MY ROYAL NEMESIS
Have you heard of the ill-omened star?
I'm sure you all remember
the recent cosmic show
where a total solar eclipse
and a comet appeared together.
Well, that comet is
still in the sky today.
That's really amazing.
Three hundred years ago,
when our ancestors noticed a comet
lingering for two months,
they called it the ill-omened star.
The herald of a villainess
who brings disaster.
You pity me?
I guess he just can't ignore that woman.
THE WOMAN POSSESSED BY KIM DU-HAN
Unit 203?
What the…
She's resorted to throwing punches now.
So, take a good look around you.
You never know.
You might discover there's
a wicked woman living right next door.
I have to keep my distance from her.
That woman just creeps me out.
He’s going to get
seriously tangled up with her.
Why do our paths keep crossing?
I'm about to lose it.
EPISODE 5
FORBIDDEN FRUIT
DAEBAK BOARDING HOUSE
She acts like she's so smart.
Did she just get scammed
by her realtor or what?
There's not even an elevator here.
And the lights don't even work.
Are you crying?
Are you really crying,
hunched over like that?
What?
Why are you back to pick another fight?
That's more like the Shin Seo-ri I know.
So she's just some random model,
nothing more?
Yes, sir.
He was initially opposed to it,
but Director Jang
strongly recommended her.
Really?
I should've known better.
What was he thinking,
linking my Se-gye with that woman?
Are you still checking if you're unfazed?
I think this is more than enough.
No, I finished a while ago,
but you were staying so still.
I just thought you were still checking.
I finished a while ago too.
Yeah?
So what's the conclusion?
Must you press me like a debt collector?
I already told you.
I see in black or white.
You're either an ally or an enemy.
I hate it when men and women
end up in that "just friends" gray area.
So give it to me straight.
Why should I go first? You answer first.
Well…
All right.
It’s cowardly for a man
to expect a woman to make the first move.
I hate it when things get predictable.
All right.
I decided it's a green light
for me.
You turned on a lantern?
I've decided to pursue you.
Jeez.
How do you feel?
Honored, right?
Heir to the Chail Group
and the finest face
in the corporate world.
I've had plenty of people declare
their love for me,
but I've never gone
on the offensive like this.
It seems you're so touched,
you can't even find the words.
Well, I understand.
Your heart must've skipped a beat,
and your nerve endings
must be tingling like crazy, right?
Relish it.
Because this is
a once-in-a-lifetime opportunity
for a woman like you.
I did not feel any tingling.
It probably hasn't sunk in yet.
You're still reeling from the shock.
Give it five minutes.
Even your fingertips will tingle.
Shin Seo-ri, you won't sleep tonight.
I feel absolutely nothing.
Even when we embraced, I felt nothing.
That's impossible.
You were just in the arms of a guy
like me, dripping with pheromones.
Don't lie, Shin Seo-ri.
Don't put up a front now
and regret it later.
This is no front.
I was just born strong-willed.
Also,
I do not go around telling needless lies.
Wait, are you serious?
You really feel nothing?
-Even after I hugged you?
-Nothing.
That can't be right.
You definitely should've felt what I felt.
I wasn't going to ask you this,
but have you been perpetually single
your whole life?
"Perpetually single"?
Have you never dated a man before?
As if.
At this age? With this beauty?
Like men would have left me alone.
-Ridiculous.
-Right?
Yeah.
Then why didn't you feel anything with me?
Does asking repeatedly change anything?
I do not see you as a man.
That must be what it means.
Wait, what?
It is raining! Oh my.
Keep a close eye on him.
Mun-do wouldn't mention baseless rumors.
That woman he saw at the TV station.
Find out who she is.
At the station? Then it can only be her.
True to your name, Degenerate.
Even if it is raining,
you cannot just walk into the home
of a single woman who lives alone.
-You really felt nothing?
-Are you still on that?
That is right. I felt nothing.
It was less thrilling
than hugging a stray mutt.
"A mutt"?
So stop moping around
and go home!
Maybe you felt nothing
because it was too quick.
You've been single for too long.
Your romantic instincts are dead.
It sounds like you need a warm-up.
Let's try again. Then I'm sure you'll--
This is getting pitiful.
Just stop, Cha Se-gye.
"Pitiful"?
Me?
They say never chase a maiden
who has walked away.
This is my home,
so just let it go gracefully.
After not dating for so long,
you must've become
romantically impotent.
You must know an opportunity like this
is rarer than winning the lottery.
Even with three generations of good karma,
the chances of such a jackpot are slim.
For one, I am not impotent.
And affection, love,
and marriage in this lifetime?
I want no part of any of that.
I never want to get involved
with a man again.
So stop being so pathetically clingy.
Jeez.
"Pathetically"?
Damn,
you must think you have
the upper hand now or something.
Shin Seo-ri, that's one hell
of a shift in attitude.
What you just said.
I've permanently etched it
into my frontal lobe.
You can't ever take it back.
Do not worry about that.
Even in a game of janggi,
I have never once asked
to take back a move.
You're so damn immersed
in this Joseon woman roleplay
that you must've lost touch with reality.
I will make sure…
you regret this moment
for the rest of your life.
I will.
Damn it.
My heart was about
to jump out of my chest.
Why the hell
would he just embrace me like that?
Don't you have an umbrella?
No, I do not!
What does this dump even have?
What is wrong with my home?
It even has a clear view of Namsan Tower!
DAEBAK BOARDING HOUSE
Who the hell did this?!
That's a nasty scratch.
The repair cost will be insane.
You checked the dashcam, right?
Just take it in for repairs later.
Even a chaebol shouldn't let
something like this slide.
Just forget it.
That dashcam might as well be a tin can.
You didn't turn it on?
How does someone as thorough
as you forget something like this?
Do you really think I just forgot?
I turned it off on purpose.
I mean, why would I leave evidence
they could use against me?
It's the dashcam footage nailing people
in these power-trip scandals.
Straight to the prosecutors
with nowhere to run.
You should never leave a trail
to begin with.
You're way too paranoid.
BUILT-IN CAM
NO MEMORY CARD
Sir, don't tell me
you don't trust me either.
In today's world, isn't this level
of distrust the default?
I don't trust anyone in this world.
You are not exempt.
I only trust myself, no one else.
You'll have a lonely life
if you keep living that way.
I've had everything I could ever want.
What do I have to be lonely about?
You don't have a woman.
Destined to die alone.
-Mr. Son.
-Yes, sir.
It seems like I've let you
get too comfortable lately.
We seem to have lost
all sense of hierarchy.
-Watch yourself.
-I will watch myself.
-Keep your eyes on the road.
-Keeping my eyes on the road.
-Seer.
-Yes?
I assume you prepared what I asked for?
Of course.
There we go.
Hold the elevator.
Oh my. Good morning, Mr. Cha.
Ms. Kim, you seem
awfully happy with life these days.
"I don't smile because I'm happy.
I smile to be happy."
That is my motto.
You have time to gleefully find happiness
and energy to spare, I see.
Then we can just cancel
your PTO this month, right?
My PTO…
I already booked a trip to Saipan
for my father-in-law's 70th.
You have to go to that.
Pass him my congratulations.
They will appreciate a cozy getaway
without their daughter-in-law.
Graciously sending them off on their own.
Isn't that true filial piety?
Mr. Son, there's something
I don't understand.
Why do we need snacks
and coffee in the break room?
It's for staff welfare purposes.
That's what salaries are for, isn't it?
Should we be dedicating
such prime real estate
to a snack corner just so employees
can munch away on company time?
Close the break room immediately.
Why is he in rabid dog mode again?
Just when things were looking up.
Be careful at times like this.
He's the type to let things build up
and explode all at once.
-Mr. Son.
-Sir.
I like those quick reflexes, Mr. Son.
Stay on full standby.
He's sick in the head.
Is your cheek okay?
I gave that punk Se-gye a real scolding.
Swinging at people like some common thug…
I'm fine, Uncle.
Mun-do, I must ask you to be
the bigger person.
Don't worry. I understand.
More importantly, the press release
for the Songjin Resort groundbreaking
was received well.
It's all thanks to your foresight.
How many struggling subsidiaries
have you resurrected already?
With you providing such solid support,
I think it's about time
we start looking
into the group succession issue.
Just wrap up the resort deal well.
Yes, sir.
Chairman, Attorney Choi is here.
Okay.
-You can go now.
-Yes, Uncle.
They're notarized documents.
They outline the full transfer
of Chairman Cha's shareholding
across all subsidiaries,
holding company included,
to Mr. Cha Se-gye.
Does Se-gye know?
Inheritance notarization can be processed
with just a resident ID number.
No consent required.
Chairman Cha didn't want
Mr. Cha to know about it.
Our Chairman…
sure loves his grandson fiercely.
Will using coagulated ox blood like this
really ward off bad luck?
We must work with what we have got.
You know, after 20 years as a seer,
there's one thing I've learned.
The cumulative law of suffering
does indeed exist.
You found a job
and even found yourself a home.
I mean, just look at you.
Seems like your days of hardship
are nearly done.
Good luck invites bad. Such is life.
Yes, of course.
People will always find a way to stab you
in the back when you let your guard down.
I am doing this warding ritual
so I can at least have some peace of mind.
What warding ritual?
At age 12, the day I was sold off
for my father's gambling debt,
I learned my first life lesson.
What a gloomy face on this girl.
Bad luck written all over it.
Keep acting this way,
and there will be
nothing left of you to find.
Jeez.
Do not worry.
Being a slave to a noble family
that keeps you fed
beats starving at home
a hundred times over.
Here.
Go on. Have some.
Just try it.
Crying on an empty stomach
will only exhaust you.
My goodness.
Free kindness always comes with a price.
Here. That is plenty.
Come on, I deserve
five more nyang for her.
Look at that pretty face.
She will seduce plenty of men
when she grows up.
If you sell her
to a courtesan house later,
she will fetch you enough
to buy a house in Bukchon.
-Trust me on this.
-Really? A house?
Never trust a hand
reached out with a smile.
-What?
-Hey!
-Where are you going?
You brat!
Damn it.
Unbelievable.
Goodness.
Lock her in the shed.
Do not give her a drop of water.
I swore to myself back then
that I would never trust
anyone but myself.
That I would never be sold off
like livestock again.
I'm rooting for you two.
I can promise you a real future.
A life of comfort.
Wait, is someone trying
to sell you off here too?
He promised a hefty reward
if I agreed to be sold.
I will not make the mistake of falling
for such sweet talk ever again.
But don't you think
you'll get a little lonely
if you live your life like that?
Not all of them will turn out
to be scammers.
Are you okay? Are you hurt anywhere?
The world may be a harsh place,
but not everyone in it means you harm.
That is why I must steel my resolve.
Scammer or not,
once your heart wavers, you become weak.
In my current situation,
weakness means the end.
Thus, I have decided.
In this life, I will not trust anyone.
Instead, I shall become
a wealthy Buddhist nun
on a path to enlightenment.
A wealthy… Buddhist nun, you say?
The only constant in this world is money.
Ought we not serve it?
When I open my window,
I can already see Namsan Tower.
I escaped that dump
in the blink of an eye,
so I shall use this momentum to soar high.
Sounds good!
She feels nothing for me?
Acting tough is only cute up to a point.
She's the one who messed with my head
with that letter and everything.
I've never been so humiliated in my life.
Known as the heir to one of the top 30…
What now?
Controversy is brewing
after it was revealed
that Mr. Cha repeatedly used
intimidation tactics
while acquiring a small business
for his startup brand launch.
You're going to have to.
This is your first and last chance
to get even a pittance
for that measly company of yours.
The price drops by a billion won
every ten seconds.
Even now, thinking about being
extorted and bled dry
by someone young enough to be my son
cuts me to the core.
The spokesperson stressed it is time
for the Fair Trade Commission
to crack down and put an end
to these diabolical acts of preying
on the small businesses
that keep Korea's economy running.
I let you off with money instead
of handcuffs, and this is what I get?
I stole your livelihood?
He must've found out the raw materials
got FDA approval right after the sale,
leaving him feeling bitter.
I'm in the headlines a lot lately.
Any stock impact?
It's plateauing around 87,000 won,
but they haven't
publicly identified you yet.
I'll have the legal team handle it
before it becomes a risk factor.
Don't worry.
No, I should worry.
Without any upward catalysts
before the launch,
even 80,000 won is precarious.
Leave the legal team out of it.
We'll tackle this head-on.
-"Head-on"?
-He's not relying on legalities right now.
He's looking to whip up public sentiment.
Then we go eye for an eye.
Forget the law.
We need to rattle his nerves.
Leak it all to the tabloids.
The photos of him gallivanting
around Kangwon Land Casino
after pocketing employee bonuses
and every last piece of evidence
of the cheap raw material swap.
Expose that fake saint
for the fraud he is.
Yes, sir.
RUTHLESS CHAEBOL STEALS
LIVELIHOOD OF SMALL BUSINESSES
I keep them out of prison,
and they stab me in the back.
Nobody knows how to be grateful anymore.
Thank you.
I have met many people here,
but you have been the kindest to me,
and I am most thankful.
That is right. I felt nothing.
It was less thrilling
than hugging a stray mutt.
Does she suffer
from multiple personalities?
Hot one minute, cold the next.
Is she playing hard to get or something?
She's actually playing hard to get.
-Manager Gu.
-She took it too far.
-Uncle!
-Manager Gu.
-Uncle.
-Uncle!
-Wake up, Uncle.
-What?
-Uncle, wake up.
-What's up?
You need to deal
with that mess on the roof!
I've told her so many times
to watch the noise!
What the… What is all this?
Rooftop, what in the world is going on…
Hail, boundless life!
Hail, the Great Spirit!
Manager Gu.
Oh my God!
Manager Gu, are you here
to watch the ritual
and grab some free rice cakes?
B-Bloo… B-Blood…
Right. This is not human blood.
It is coagulated ox blood.
Why would you put on
such a terrifying getup?
I'm about to enter the battlefield,
so I thought I would put some on
to ward off evil.
Want some, Manager Gu?
What was today's closing price?
It closed at 82,000 won.
With today's leak making the rounds,
numbers are down slightly
after the deepfake scandal.
Meaning we can't afford any more bad news.
For now, send this out with the photos.
Just to the tabloids,
including financial gossip rags.
Skip mainstream outlets.
Is that necessary when the PR team
already tipped off the deputy managers
about the raw material swap?
What we need isn't a news story.
We just need a good story.
We're throwing bait
for the public to bite,
so we need to spice it up.
I should've known.
Your disarmingly cunning tactics
are on another level, sir.
-Speaking of which, Mr. Son.
-Yes, sir.
Never mind.
Yes, sir.
Damn it.
Mr. Son, I have a question.
Yes, sir. Go ahead.
Well…
-Never mind.
-"Never mind"?
Gosh.
Jeez. What is it? Just tell me.
You've been keeping me
in suspense all day.
Mr. Son, did you just yell at me?
No, of course not.
I wasn't yelling.
I was just urging you to tell me
so you'd be less stressed.
That there is no need for you
to agonize over it.
It was an earnest plea, sir.
Since you're pushing so hard, Mr. Son,
I'll be frank with you.
Between a man and a woman…
when it comes to the push-and-pull,
how do you gain the upper hand?
"The push-and-pull"?
It's the storyline of some drama
I've been watching when I can't sleep.
I just leave it on to fall asleep to.
Well!
The way I see it, timing is everything
when playing hard to get.
The reality is,
you just have to bombard them.
Give them no time to play games.
Because love
is just another form of warfare.
By bombardment, do you mean
just overwhelming them
with a massive offensive?
In the war of courtship,
losing is winning.
Just say,
"I surrender! I'll die without you!"
When you throw away all your pride,
that's when you truly gain the upper hand.
So what about you?
Have you won every battle
using that method?
I've lost every battle.
Theory is just theory, after all.
-Let's go.
-Right away, sir.
A full-on bombardment
and a massive offensive…
As if you could ever gain the upper hand
with such a cliché strategy.
Isn't there anything else?
No. What don't you like about this one?
It doesn't fit quite right.
It doesn't look sharp.
It's the exact same cut
as your usual custom jackets.
Is it just me?
It just feels cliché.
I am finally entering the battlefield.
GRANDMA
Who…
are you?
Seo-ri, it's Grandma.
Are you doing okay up there?
I am fine.
But is everything okay there?
Is anyone causing trouble again?
No, of course not.
You chased them all away.
But since when were you so agile?
Well, I…
I picked up a few things here and there.
If they swarm in again,
call me right away, okay?
Okay, I will.
Gosh, I have customers.
Don't worry about me, okay?
Make sure you eat well.
Okay, I'm hanging up now.
Seo-ri.
How does it feel to be on set?
It must feel really different,
stepping onto the set this time
as Court Lady Kim,
instead of "Palace Attendant 28."
You only scored a role like this
because you have me.
I am not even the Head Court Lady.
Stop making such a fuss.
Not even a single line.
Even without a single line,
you can steal the scene
with just one look, okay?
-Do your best.
-Did you check continuity?
-Yes, confirmed.
-And the CGI?
Gosh. Ms. Hong.
-Director, how have you been?
-You get prettier by the day.
-Who cares about effort?
-You're too sweet.
Results are what matter.
Shin Seo-ri.
You finally got a role, thanks to me.
You should give it your all
and try to hide that you pulled strings.
If you wish for me to do well,
do not hover around me pointlessly.
That face of yours remains
my only irritant in this place.
But remember,
when the cameras are rolling,
I am the Queen,
and you are just a lowly court lady.
Even I can't save you if you can't act.
-Let's go.
-This way.
As if.
Why, that minx…
She is putting on airs
just because she is in the Queen's garb.
What's taking so long?
Oh my God!
Gosh. Oh no…
I'm so sorry.
You should watch where you're going.
I'll pay for the dry cleaning.
No, I'll pay for the suit.
You should find out how much it is
before you offer to pay for it.
I'm a regular here too, so I know.
It's my fault, so I should compensate you.
I'll pass on that offer.
I'm not so poor that I need
to beg for free clothes.
Sir.
-Are you okay?
-Wait, what happened…
Please step this way first.
Just get me a fresh one. Same suit.
And send the rest to my house.
But you just got custom suits last week.
Why buy so many jackets again--
Do you starve today
because you ate yesterday?
Don't get me wrong.
I appreciate the business.
This will be my armor.
I've got a battle coming up
that I refuse to lose.
When mating season arrives
in the animal kingdom,
a fierce war of courtship begins.
To seduce a female of their liking,
most males will shower
the females with gifts.
However, some animals seduce females
by showing off their flashy looks.
The male peacock is one of them.
He raises his tail feathers
to show off his beauty.
Just look at him flap those wings.
The peacock flaps its wings desperately
to avoid being left behind.
In this courtship battle
for the female's favor,
will this male emerge victorious?
The results will be revealed
in 60 seconds.
Mi-rae, what's the food truck
serving today?
Darn it. It's spicy stir-fried pork again.
-I like spicy pork.
-Sounds delicious.
Look at Shin Seo-ri beaming and glowing.
You even got a name this time.
"Court Lady Kim So-yun."
Wow…
You are that palace maid.
It has been a while.
I see you have earned the right
to wear a gache.
Oh right.
Yeah, I'm playing a minor court lady too.
I heard you renewed your contract
and landed this role?
How did you ever manage to win Hong over?
She was totally ready
to terminate your contract before.
Why the sudden renewal?
Do not drag up old history.
People ought to live looking ahead.
Excuse me.
She's got this weird aura now.
GONG TAE-WOO'S SURPRISE ROMANCE
My poor head.
-I'm about to get a cramp.
-Damn it.
Hey, are we shooting Scene 36 today?
Gong Tae-woo.
Do I really have to see
your cheating trending online?
You'd better text back
while I'm still asking nicely.
Ji-hyo, wasn't she
your stand-in last time?
The one who had the meltdown.
Wait, isn't she Shin Seo-ri?
The lead in that old drama, Sonagi.
You're right.
"The Nation's Pebble, Shin Seo-ri."
Ji-hyo, you made your acting debut
in that drama too.
What? Ji-hyo was in that too?
Yeah, she was
the class president in another class.
The annoying girl who always
bullied the female lead--
That's ancient history!
Have you forgotten the part
where her career tanked six months later
because she can't act?
Damn it.
What the hell is she doing
with the assistant director anyway?
Listen here.
Those two hanging around that minx.
Are they supposed to be
Consorts Su-gui and So-yong?
Excuse me? "Minx"?
I mean Yoon Ji-hyo.
I believe that minx is playing
the role of the Queen.
Why does the Queen's hair look like that?
And why are those underlings
wearing gaches en masse?
-What about it?
-During King Anjong's reign,
the ban on gaches was issued.
So I ask you
because those Inner Court minions
are all proudly wearing their gaches.
Change them at once.
I mean, who are you to demand
we make changes?
I mean…
What are you doing here?
I told you to get the cinematographer.
Well, this woman
was spouting nonsense about the gaches.
How dare you! "Nonsense"?
Even if moral standards have hit
rock bottom in Hell Joseon,
should we not at least strive
for historical accuracy?
Excuse me.
You were the stand-in
for Royal Consort Jang last time, right?
"Jang"? I am of the Kang clan!
Look at that projection.
Great commanding tone.
Thanks to that commanding tone,
our drama shorts got a lot of buzz.
But that one viral moment has got you
way too committed to the bit.
You're in too deep. You can't do that.
Are you the chief here?
Right, I'm the chief…
"Chief"?
I have been utterly unable
to reason with this dunce.
Your presence is most welcome.
Let us go somewhere quiet
and have a frank discussion.
Director, what's going on?
Ji-hyo. She's an actor
from your agency, right?
Where is Ms. Hong? Go get Ms. Hong.
She needs to keep her actors in check.
This is unacceptable.
Oh my, did Seo-ri already make
some sort of mistake?
I'm so sorry.
I know we're from the same agency,
but I did warn them
against pulling strings for her.
I'm mortified as the lead of this drama.
As if.
This is why
I say you can't fix up
an old, washed-up rookie.
Didn't I, you dunce?
You cast her, didn't you?
She must be a favor hire.
Jeez. No wonder.
These wretches dare to publicly shame me
to my very face.
Listen, since Ji-hyo
is speaking up for you,
I'll let it slide this once.
But there won't be a second time.
You should offer her a deep bow.
-What?
-No need.
It's fine, Director. Please calm down.
The crew is working so hard.
Let me treat everyone to iced Americanos
to celebrate the start of Season 2.
Let's get back to it.
-Look here, Chief.
-She's not a favor hire.
-"Chief"? Did she really call me that?
-Come on, Director.
What's her name again? Seo-ri?
Cut! Okay, next scene!
Great work, everyone.
Look at that minx asserting her dominion
and marking her territory.
It is both infuriating and grating.
Swiftly rising to distinction
is my only option.
Ms. Shin Seo-ri.
-Thanks for the latte.
-Thank you.
-Good luck, Seo-ri.
-Thanks for the drink.
-Thank you.
-Thanks for the treat.
What the…
Why are they suddenly being so nice?
The number you have dialed is unavailable.
You will be transferred to voicemail…
Now he's blocked me?
That scumbag. Damn it.
Go get me an iced Americano.
-Overflowing with ice.
-Okay.
Yes, sure. Thank you.
Hey, the delivery is going to be delayed
because it's lunchtime.
-Isn't that what you ordered?
-What?
Someone else sent a coffee truck?
I'll cancel our order right away.
Really?
The lead should kick it off.
Who could be this thoughtless?
Wait. Hold on a second.
"Courtesy of Shin Seo-ri,
the acting virtuoso"?
Ji-hyo.
Did Shin Seo-ri send a coffee truck?
COURTESY OF SHIN SEO-RI
THE ACTING VIRTUOSO
SHIN SEO-RI'S QUEENDOM OF BEAUTY
-This is me. Right here.
-Seo-ri, you look beautiful.
Please look over here.
You're so pretty. I'm a fan.
-Could I get a picture?
-Sure.
Thank you.
Thank you, Seo-ri. Thanks for the treat.
-Thanks for the treat.
-Thank you, everyone.
In my entire life,
I have never before received
gratitude from such a horde at once.
It is a hundred times better
than being treated like dirt.
Seo-ri, you're so pretty.
I am Shin Seo-ri.
I am the Shin Seo-ri.
Now, smile.
How does it feel, Shin Seo-ri?
Are you finally feeling
that tsunami of emotion?
Cha Se-gye?
Don't say my name out loud.
Wait…
Was this all your doing, Cha Se-gye?
Seriously? I just told you
to stop saying my name.
You scoundrel.
Ms. Hong.
You paired Shin Seo-ri up with me
without saying anything,
and now you're even sending coffee trucks?
Have you ever seen me waste my money?
There's a proper order to everything.
Why would I get one for her first?
Hold on. So it really wasn't you?
-No.
-Then,
who the hell wasted their money on that?
Maybe a fan sent it.
Since when does she have fans?
Damn it.
I mean…
What are you plotting now?
What scheme are you hatching
that requires such bribery?
I suppose you could call it a bribe.
There is an ulterior motive.
"Ulterior motive"?
Now you are finally showing
your true colors.
You are not a fan or an ally,
yet you pretended to care.
What is your ulterior motive?
As of today,
I'm officially setting this as my target.
My heart.
What are you going to do to it?
Yeah. I'm going to steal your heart.
You said you felt nothing.
That I moved you less than a stray mutt.
I haven't slept for days after that.
It got to me.
Whether you sleep or do handstands,
what does that have to do with me?
Look at you, acting tough again.
The thing is,
I realized I overlooked something.
And what is that?
That a woman like you, Shin Seo-ri,
is far from innocent.
Are you saying I am dirty and vulgar?
You're a skilled liar.
You'll use any means necessary
to achieve your goals.
In short, you're a dangerous woman.
So are you going to be petty now
and suggest we cancel our contract?
But the thing is,
I've never been one to lose.
So I'm confident
I won't lose this time either.
Maybe not?
Is he looking for a fight?
-Is this retaliation?
-No, it's a surrender.
They say in love and war,
sometimes losing is winning.
What is with this intense stare?
Look, I admit I skipped
the romantic gestures
and acted a bit rashly.
So let's wipe the slate clean
and start over.
What is with this duplicity?
Cold and ruthless to the core,
yet those eyes are nothing but sincere.
Could he be…
Do you… truly harbor affection for me?
I do.
Why is this fool
charging in headfirst like this?
I get it. You're a woman,
so accepting right away
would hurt your pride.
I'll give you a day to protect your ego.
No need.
Here is my definitive answer.
It has never changed,
and I guarantee it never will.
Cha Se-gye.
I harbor
no affection for you.
Not now, not ever, until the end of time.
Oh my.
That wicked degenerate.
Launching a surprise attack
in close combat.
I am a Buddhist nun.
A Buddhist nun with long hair.
Hey, Shin Seo-ri.
You take this.
The smell is giving me a headache.
You…
Did you buy flowers too?
Don't read into it. It's annoying.
What's that about?
That's a supercar.
Shin Seo-ri, that loser, has a boyfriend?
You dare reject me?
Not just once, but twice?
CHIEF OF STAFF SON JAE-HAN
Sir, you're on your way, right?
Today is the dinner
at the Chairman's estate.
-Did you perhaps forget--
-Do you have any idea
the humiliation I just suffered
because of you, Mr. Son?
Wait, what did I do--
That's on me for asking
a cat-cuddling old bachelor.
Damn it.
Oh my, I'm so sorry. Are you okay?
-It's you, right?
-What?
Earlier at the shop.
Don't you remember?
Shop? What shop?
Have we met?
The coffee at the tailor shop.
I spilled coffee on you.
Right, that coffee.
You seem to be quite accident-prone.
I don't think my face is that forgettable.
Don't say no a second time. Call me.
Aftereffects of a car accident
are what get you.
-"Trinice"?
-It's my company.
I've got enough money not to hit
someone's car and just drive off,
so make sure to bill me
for your treatment.
An epic clash
of relentlessly stubborn titans.
Is this the age-old battle
of spear versus shield?
Weren't you the one who told me
to stop going on blind dates?
I've already struck out in that world
and been blacklisted there.
You may have struck out domestically,
but the overseas market
remains an untapped goldmine.
Counter twisted logic
by twisting your own.
Does scrap metal turn into silver
just by crossing an ocean, Grandfather?
Stop complaining and make time this week.
I don't even mind
if she can't speak Korean well.
Utilize false reasoning
and distortion to force
the desired conclusion.
I really don't have the time.
Grandfather, are you trying
to pull a ruse?
I almost fell for it.
Sharp-eyed devil.
You were so hopeless at blind dates.
I figured you were more
of an organic meeting type.
Was that so terrible of me?
"Organic." How hip.
If she's willing to play along
with this ridiculous act,
it's obvious what she's like.
Either naive or stupid.
She's a smart young lady
who's perfect for you.
That's why I changed my mind.
You must have met her first.
If she's that great, you should marry her.
What? You rotten punk!
When you're outmatched,
go for the jugular.
A foolproof strategy for victory.
I do.
Jeez.
Did he really think some common flowers
would sway me in the slightest?
My welfare is my first priority.
And my second.
In this life,
I will be sure to guard my heart
and live out my days to the fullest.
Dan-sim of the Kang clan.
Your Highness, what brings you here?
These are my secret quarters.
What are you doing here?
I was just…
What are you burying?
Did you bury a stolen trinket?
I did not steal anything.
Do you take me for some petty thief?
There, the spark is back in your eyes.
Do not sulk like some mutt
caught in the rain.
You are only yourself when you are feisty.
Speaking of,
where did that mutt go?
Did you chase it away?
Or… is it dead?
It died.
I killed it.
That cannot be true.
If you had indeed killed it,
you would not be looking so distraught,
making a grave for it.
Let us at least pray
for this nameless dog's soul.
So that it may find peace
in the afterlife.
May you
be reborn as a human in your next life
and live out your days to the fullest.
May you live out your days to the fullest.
Why did he have to give me these?
But they are still living things.
I cannot just throw them away.
It'd be a waste to toss out flowers.
Someone must've asked her out.
Did Unit 204 give it to you?
Be quiet.
Enough chattering.
Hang your laundry and go.
Jeez. What's with the attitude?
Did you watch
The Women's Kingdom yesterday?
I can't believe Season 2 started.
Yoon Ji-hyo got even prettier.
-Her skin is flawless.
-She must spend a fortune on it.
That minx's glowing skin
is just caked-on makeup.
What the… You tell us
to be quiet, then chime in?
She's just dissing her out of jealousy.
As if she's ever seen her.
Of course I have. I saw her yesterday.
Where?
Probably at her part-time gig.
Rooftop is an actor too. A wannabe.
-Stop lying.
-It's true. She goes to film sets.
You think just anyone can be an actor?
Those brats.
I give them my yard for their laundry
and get zero gratitude.
Damn it.
This is why you should never
carelessly let someone in.
I'll be sending the schedule
for the Jeju Island shoot in two days,
so pack your bags.
Ji-hyo is on vacation, so I'll let you use
her van and road manager for now.
Take advantage of that.
I refuse anything that belongs
to that minx.
I shall carefully handpick my own person,
so be aware.
Can't sleep lately?
Every time I lie down,
I get so mad that I can't fall asleep.
Lying in bed and suddenly cringing
at the past is normal.
Turn off your brain. Maybe meditate.
How can I turn it off?
I've never been so insulted in my life.
Yeah, the news comments are nuts,
cursing you out
and calling you a corporate raider.
I can't just let this go.
It's too humiliating.
I need revenge.
"Revenge"?
A fresh scandal always drowns out
the last one.
Just be patient.
Time will solve everything.
"Fresh scandal"?
Yeah.
That's a good way to bury it.
Thanks for the session today.
You've become a real miracle worker.
Hey, don't forget your meds!
Nurse Kim, could you take this
to Mr. Cha Se-gye?
Sure, give it to me.
Mr. Son.
Call Grandfather.
Tell him I'll go on that blind date
as soon as possible.
Mr. Cha Se-gye, your medication is ready.
No, just stop talking and do it now.
HANBIT MENTAL HEALTH CLINIC
DELIVERY COMPLETED
"In the Anglo-American legal system,
police are formed as an organization
granted autonomous authority by citizens…"
Is that good?
Jesus!
Make some noise when you walk.
You're not a ghost.
Your physique may be lacking,
but you survive on noodles day after day
and remain a penny-pincher.
Your survival skills are top-notch.
What's up?
And despite all my scolding,
you still talk back to me.
You are more tenacious than you look.
Will you place yourself in my service?
What are you talking about?
I shall
personally appoint you as my "nodo."
"Nodo"? What's that?
"No" as in "toil." "Do" as in "guide."
"To guide through toil."
Have you never heard of a "nodo" manager?
"Nodo"?
I see.
You mean "road manager"?
You think I've been working part-time gigs
day and night just to become your driver?
I'll have you know,
I graduated
from a four-year university in Seoul.
So you even possess some knowledge.
You are a perfect fit.
My standards for choosing subordinates
are quite strict,
but no matter how I look at it,
there is no talent quite like you.
Are you even listening to me?
Even if I'm desperate for money,
I'd never be crazy enough to work for you.
How much would satisfy you?
I will pay whatever you ask.
Pay whatever I ask?
You live in a rooftop room.
Three times your minimum wage.
Would three times satisfy you?
You think you can just buy me with money?
I won't do it! No way!
Damn it.
I screwed up. Royally screwed up.
Damn my need for money.
She offered triple the pay.
How could I refuse that?
What are you doing? Move yourself quickly!
Have you never been to Jeju?
Why are you so dressed up?
And what's with the weird glasses?
As a celebrity,
one must never let one's guard down,
even at departure.
Are the reporters not here yet?
"Departure"?
By the way, I saw online
that the CEO of the company
you're shooting the commercial for
is getting a ton of hate for being
morally corrupt and controversial.
-You sure about this?
-What does it matter?
As long as we are making money.
Then again, that would be the pot
calling the kettle black. Who's to judge?
Why, you…
There's absolutely no need for the CEO
to be there for a campaign shoot.
Out of all our marketing strategies,
isn't this ad the top priority right now?
The advertiser should be there on set,
overseeing things directly.
I was hoping to sneak in
some long-overdue PTO on this work trip.
Guess not.
Welcome aboard. Have a pleasant flight.
Welcome aboard.
If you live long enough,
you really do see it all.
A marvel to fly through the skies
while still very much alive.
This will do.
The seats are so plush.
I can sleep with both legs stretched out.
Why do you walk so fast?
I told you to wait for me.
It is your feet that are slow.
I have saved us good seats.
Sit down quickly.
What?
These aren't our seats. Get up.
They are not?
Then where are our seats?
Come on. Let's go.
Those seats over there
were nice and roomy.
Why is it so cramped here?
Because that was business class.
This is economy.
You could've just paid extra
if you liked it that much.
So they divide the seats based on money?
Is that what you are saying?
This wretched Hell Joseon.
Let's keep it moving.
-Sorry.
-What are they even doing?
-Hurry up and sit down. Just sit.
-So cramped.
Miserable bastards.
Why not make it clear from the start?
Beggars, commoners, and noblemen.
They might as well label the sections.
Listen, I've been meaning to
ask you something for a while now.
Did you actually finish
your compulsory education?
Because your English seems a bit lacking.
I am fluent in the language
of the mainland.
I have mastered
both the Sohak and the Analects.
Right. So your English is lacking.
Sir,
your recent insomnia
is work-related, right?
Or maybe something shifted personally?
Why?
Did Grandfather call you in
and grill you again?
No, sir. Nothing like that happened.
You won't be grilled anymore.
I decided to grant his wish, remember?
Why did you suddenly change your mind?
You said you were too busy.
Well, I found a need
for it myself as well.
It's a win-win situation.
It's a bit hot in here, though.
Is it just me?
I need to move around a bit.
Excuse me.
-Could he get a glass of cold water?
-Right away.
Goodness.
Jeez.
Please just sit still.
The person in front is staring.
It feels like I paid money to be tortured.
I would rather have my legs twisted.
Did you only ever fly business class?
Just hang in there.
I'm going to use the restroom.
Shoot!
You scoundrel! You wretched scoundrel!
Pardon me. Sorry.
I was thrilled to fly through the skies,
only to find myself tied down
and imprisoned.
Gosh. It's so stifling.
May I have your attention please?
We have a medical emergency on board.
Any medical professionals,
please see a flight attendant.
Thank you.
Any doctors or nurses?
Is anyone a doctor or a nurse?
A doctor?
We really appreciate you stepping up.
We were so worried.
Thank goodness we had a doctor on board.
You say a life is in grave danger.
It is man's duty to preserve
even the life of his enemy.
Eastern medicine?
I am known for my healing hands.
Even during my palace maid days,
palace nurses lined up for me to prick
their fingers to relieve indigestion.
One, two, three, four.
-Right here.
-Five, six.
-The doctor is here.
-Seven, eight. Three, two, three.
Six, seven, eight.
Cha Se-gye?
Hey, Cha Se-gye!
Why are you sprawled out like this?
Do you know him? Thank goodness.
Pricking his finger will not be enough.
Cha Se-gye, breathe. Come on.
Cha Se-gye!
What are you doing? Please start CPR!
What? "Sipper"?
Hold on.
Oh no…
Come on, Cha Se-gye!
Breathe, come on!
Cha Se-gye!
Passengers, the aircraft
is experiencing turbulence…
What are you doing? Hurry!
Please fasten your seatbelts.
Ladies and gentlemen…
What the…
What are you doing right now?
Cha Se-gye!
Cha Se-gye, wake up!
Wake up!
Cha Se-gye!
Come on, Cha Se-gye!
Cha Se-gye.
Are you finally coming to your senses?
Goodness, I really thought you were
about to cross into the afterlife.
You…
-Poison…
-What poison?
Tonic? Toxin?
I cannot hear you. Speak up!
Rat poison.
Rat poison?
You're toxic, like poison.
Cha Se-gye!
Have you gone mad?
Open your eyes! Cha Se-gye!
Cha Se-gye!
Where's the AED?
I have it.
No! Don't die, Cha Se-gye!
Cha Se-gye!
You cannot die!
Cha Se-gye, do not leave me!
No, please do not die!
-Everyone, step back.
-No, do not die!
-Cha Se-gye, no!
-One, two, three!
No--
Oh no…
My welfare is my first priority.
And my second.
In this life, I will be sure
to guard my heart
and live out my days to the fullest.
MY ROYAL NEMESIS
Here.
Become my brother's lover.
You must have cherished this dog greatly.
I am sure it is grateful.
Thanks to you,
its life here was a little less lonely.
Dan-sim of the Kang clan.
This flower suits you.
It stands out, so it is perfect for you.
Do not be too heartbroken.
Why not seek out a true companion
instead of a dog that cannot speak?
Shall I be
that companion for you?
Have I finally crossed over
to the afterlife?
Could this be paradise?
If I am doing this, I might as well
go all out and show it all off.
Change her outfit. Next. Swap.
Are your eyes possessed or something?
She's the only thing I can see right now!
Why are you nitpicking
every little thing today?
Just because I rejected your affections,
you hound me all damn day?
I am truly glad to be alive.
Drink up!
It seems the time has come.
Take care of her quietly.
Is Seo-ri still not answering?
You saw her? Where?
Where is she right now?
Subtitle translation by Justin S. Kim